Guide to the Boone and Crockett Club Records circa 1885-2009
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana-Missoula
- Big Game Records, 1906-2002; Series III; 29.75 linear feet
  - Awards Programs and Competitions, 1947-2001; Subseries 2; 8.0 linear feet
    - 16th North American Big Game Awards, Invitations and Printed Materials, 1977 (Box-folder 151/14)
    - 16th North American Big Game Awards, Invitation of Trophies, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 151/15)
    - 16th North American Big Game Awards, Judges and Consultants, 1977 (Box-folder 151/16)
    - 16th North American Big Game Awards, Official Measurers, Correspondence, 1977 (Box-folder 152/1)
    - 16th North American Big Game Awards, Photograph Brochure Galley, 1977 (Box-folder 152/2)
    - 16th North American Big Game Awards, Press Day Invitations, 1977 (Box-folder 152/3)
    - 16th North American Big Game Awards, Program, 1977 (Box-folder 152/4)
    - 16th North American Big Game Awards, Publicity Outlets, 1974 (Box-folder 152/5)
    - 16th North American Big Game Awards, Requests for Banquet Tickets, 1977 (Box-folder 152/6)
    - 16th North American Big Game Awards, Specific Trophy Problems, 1973-1978 (Box-folder 152/7)
    - 16th North American Big Game Awards, Trophy Receipt Acknowledgements, 1977 (Box-folder 152/8)
    - 17th North American Big Game Awards, Awards Certificate, 1980 (Box-folder 152/9)
    - 17th North American Big Game Awards, Banquet Planning, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 152/10)
    - 17th North American Big Game Awards, Biographical Questionnaires, 1980 (Box-folder 152/11)
    - 17th North American Big Game Awards, Form Correspondence and Invitations, 1980 (Box-folder 152/12)
    - 17th North American Big Game Awards, Invited Trophies Roster, 1980 (Box-folder 152/13)
    - 17th North American Big Game Awards, Materials for The American Hunter, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 152/14)
    - 17th North American Big Game Awards, Photograph Brochure Program, Draft, 1980 (Box-folder 152/15)
    - 17th North American Big Game Awards, Report of Official Travel, 1980 (Box-folder 152/16)
    - 17th North American Big Game Awards, Specific Trophy Problems, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 152/17)
    - 17th North American Big Game Awards, Trophy Owners, Working Lists, circa 1980 (Box-folder 153/1)
    - 18th North American Big Game Awards, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 153/2)
    - 18th North American Big Game Awards, Flyer, Color Separations, 1983 (Box-folder 153/3)
    - 18th North American Big Game Awards, Materials, 1983 (Box-folder 153/4)
    - 18th North American Big Game Awards, Originals, 1983 (Box-folder 153/5)
    - 18th North American Big Game Awards, Program, 1983 (Box-folder 153/6)
    - 18th North American Big Game Awards, Schedule of Events, 1983 (Box-folder 153/7)
    - 18th North American Big Game Awards, Trophy Holder, Correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 153/8)
    - 19th North American Big Game Awards, Awards Banquet Invitation, Mailer, and Program, 1986 (Box-folder 153/9)
    - 19th North American Big Game Awards, Awards Banquet Planning, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 153/10)
    - 19th North American Big Game Awards, Program, 1986 (Box-folder 153/11)
    - 19th North American Big Game Awards, Specific Trophy Problems and Dispute, 1973-1985 (Box-folder 153/12-14)
    - 20th North American Big Game Awards, Awards Banquet Program and Tickets, 1989 (Box-folder 153/15)
    - 20th North American Big Game Awards, Awards Banquet Seating Chart, 1989 (Box-folder 153/16)
    - 20th North American Big Game Awards, Certificates and Programs, 1989-1992 (Box-folder 153/17)
    - 20th North American Big Game Awards, Facilities Rental Correspondence, 1988 (Box-folder 153/18)
    - 20th North American Big Game Awards, Printed Materials, Color Separations, 1989 (Box-folder OS 219/x)
    - 20th North American Big Game Awards, Registration Refunds, 1989 (Box-folder 153/19)
    - 20th North American Big Game Awards, Specific Trophy Disputes, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 153/20)
    - 21st North American Big Game Awards, Accepted Trophy, Score Sheet, 1989 (Box-folder 153/21)
    - 21st North American Big Game Awards, Auction Materials, 1992 (Box-folder 154/1)
    - 21st North American Big Game Awards, Awards Banquet Attendees Roster, 1992 (Box-folder 154/2)
    - 21st North American Big Game Awards, Brochure, 1992 (Box-folder 154/3)
    - 21st North American Big Game Awards, Brochure, Galley Proofs, 1992 (Box-folder OS 219/x)
    - 21st North American Big Game Awards, Lawrence C. Means, Contract, 1992 (Box-folder 154/4)
    - 21st North American Big Game Awards, Meeting Attendance, 1992 (Box-folder 154/5)
    - 21st North American Big Game Awards, Programs, 1992 (Box-folder 154/6)
    - 21st North American Big Game Awards, Trophy Acceptance Letter, 1992 (Box-folder 154/7)
    - 21st North American Big Game Awards, Wisconsin Bear and Buck Club, Correspondence, 1987-1991 (Box-folder 154/8)
    - 22nd North American Big Game Awards, Awards Banquet Materials, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 154/9)
    - 22nd North American Big Game Awards, Complimentary Book Lists, 1995 (Box-folder 154/10)
    - 22nd North American Big Game Awards, Complimentary Media Lists and Materials, 1995 (Box-folder 154/11)
    - 22nd North American Big Game Awards, Correspondence, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 154/12)
    - 22nd North American Big Game Awards, Donations, 1995 (Box-folder 154/13)
    - 22nd North American Big Game Awards, Hunting Stories and Authorization Forms, A-B, 1995 (Box-folder 154/14)
    - 22nd North American Big Game Awards, Hunting Stories and Authorization Forms, C, 1995 (Box-folder 154/15)
    - 22nd North American Big Game Awards, Hunting Stories and Authorization Forms, D-E, 1995 (Box-folder 154/16)
    - 22nd North American Big Game Awards, Hunting Stories and Authorization Forms, F-G, 1995 (Box-folder 154/17)
    - 22nd North American Big Game Awards, Hunting Stories and Authorization Forms, H, 1995 (Box-folder 155/1)
    - 22nd North American Big Game Awards, Hunting Stories and Authorization Forms, J-K, 1995 (Box-folder 155/2)
    - 22nd North American Big Game Awards, Hunting Stories and Authorization Forms, L, 1995 (Box-folder 155/3)
    - 22nd North American Big Game Awards, Hunting Stories and Authorization Forms, M, 1995 (Box-folder 155/4-5)
    - 22nd North American Big Game Awards, Hunting Stories and Authorization Forms, N-O, 1995 (Box-folder 155/6)
    - 22nd North American Big Game Awards, Hunting Stories and Authorization Forms, P, 1995 (Box-folder 155/7)
    - 22nd North American Big Game Awards, Hunting Stories and Authorization Forms, R, 1995 (Box-folder 156/1)
    - 22nd North American Big Game Awards, Hunting Stories and Authorization Forms, S, 1995 (Box-folder 156/2)
    - 22nd North American Big Game Awards, Hunting Stories and Authorization Forms, T-Z, 1995 (Box-folder 156/3)
    - 22nd North American Big Game Awards, Invitation and Attendee Lists, 1995 (Box-folder 156/4)
    - 22nd North American Big Game Awards, Invitation Response Forms, 1995 (Box-folder 156/5-6)
    - 22nd North American Big Game Awards, Judges/Consultants Materials, 1995 (Box-folder 156/7)
    - 22nd North American Big Game Awards, Planning, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 156/8)
    - 22nd North American Big Game Awards, Press Awards, 1995 (Box-folder 156/9)
    - 22nd North American Big Game Awards, Press Releases, 1995 (Box-folder 156/10)
    - 22nd North American Big Game Awards, Program, 1995 (Box-folder 156/11)
    - 22nd North American Big Game Awards, Sample Mailers and Meeting Materials, 1995 (Box-folder 157/1)
    - 22nd North American Big Game Awards, Volunteers, 1995 (Box-folder 157/2)
    - 23rd North American Big Game Awards, Meeting Materials, 1998 (Box-folder 157/3)
    - 23rd North American Big Game Awards, Trophy Correspondence, 1998 (Box-folder 157/4)
    - 23rd North American Big Game Awards, Trophy Invitation List, 1998 (Box-folder 157/5)
    - 24th North American Big Game Awards and Summer Quarterly Meeting Materials, 2001 (Box-folder 227/8)
    - 24th North American Big Game Awards, Category Count for All Accepted Trophies, 2000 (Box-folder 157/6)
    - 24th North American Big Game Awards, Certificate Printing, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 157/7)
    - 24th North American Big Game Awards, Judges Panel, Correspondence and Forms, 2001 (Box-folder 226/10)
    - 24th North American Big Game Awards Survey Results, undated (Box-folder 225/8)
    - 24th North American Big Game Awards, Trophy Invitation Lists, 2001 (Box-folder 226/4)
    - 24th North American Big Game Awards, Trophy Release Forms, 2001 (Box-folder 226/3)
    - 24th North American Big Game Awards, Trophy Shipping Records, 2001 (Box-folder 226/5-9)
    - Certificates, 1967 and undated (Box-folder 157/8)
  - Sagamore Hill Medal Program, 1948-1993; Subseries 3; 0.25 linear feet
    Created in 1948, the Sagamore Hill Medal is given by the Roosevelt family in honor of Theodore Roosevelt, Theodore Roosevelt, Jr., and Kermit Roosevelt. It is awarded by the Big Game Final Awards Judges panel to an outstanding trophy of distinction. Only one is given at any Big Game Awards Program and one need not be awarded at each Program. This Subseries contains certificates, correspondence and committee materials related to the Medal Program.
    - Committee to Award the Sagamore Hill Medal, 1977 (Box-folder 157/9)
    - Sagamore Hill Medal, 1962-1977 (Box-folder 157/10)
    - Sagamore Hill Medal, Certificates, undated (Box-folder 157/11)
    - Sagamore Hill Medal, Competition Judges, 1948-1975 (Box-folder 157/12)
    - Sagamore Hill Medal, Correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 157/13)
    - Sagamore Hill Medal, Memoranda, 1977 (Box-folder 241/2)
    - Sagamore Hill Medal, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1993 (Box-folder 157/14)
    - Sagamore Hill Medals and Inventory, Correspondence, 1964-1977 (Box-folder 157/15)
  - Official Measurer Materials, 1957-1998; Subseries 4; 1.5 linear feet
    Official Measurers of the Boone and Crockett Club are volunteers who are certified by the Club to measure big game trophies. All trophies entered into a Records of North American Big Game Awards Program must be measured by a Boone and Crockett Club Official Measurer. Official Measurers have been utilized by the Boone and Crockett Club since the late 1940s.
    This subseries contains correspondence between Official Measurers and Big Game Records professional staff, and the Records of North American Big Game Committee, and Official Measurer manual drafts. Of particular interest are materials related to Official Measurer training workshops developed by William H. Nesbitt, Administrative Director of the North American Big Game Records Program.
    - Advertisement of Official Measurers, 1973 and undated (Box-folder 157/16)
    - Jack N. Allen, Washington Official Measurer, Correspondence, 1963-1974 (Box-folder 157/17)
    - Annual Trophy Measurement Forms, 1972 (Box-folder 157/18)
    - Appointments, 1976 (Box-folder 157/19)
    - Big Game Records Staff, Official Measurer, Correspondence, 1993 (Box-folder 157/20)
    - Big Game Workshops, 1976 (Box-folder 157/21)
    - Conduct, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 157/22)
    - Form Letters, 1965-1973 (Box-folder 157/23)
    - Inquiries and Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 157/24)
    - Manual, 1969 (Box-folder 158/1)
    - Manual, Correspondence and Drafts, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 158/2)
    - Manual, Drafts, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 158/3)
    - Manual, Addendum, 1972 (Box-folder 158/4)
    - Materials Requested by Official Measurers, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 158/5-6)
    - Materials Sent to Official Measurers, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 158/7-8)
    - Materials Sent to Official Measurers, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 158/9)
    - Measuring Tape Production, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 158/10)
    - North American Big Game Awards Program, Official Measurers, Correspondence, 1978-1983 (Box-folder 158/11 (1 of 3))
    - North American Big Game Awards Program, Official Measurers, Correspondence, 1978-1983 (Box-folder 159/1-2 (2-3 of 3))
    - Official Measurer Master Lists, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 159/3-4)
    - Planning for Official Measurer Workshops, 1974-1982 (Box-folder 159/5-6)
    - Records of North American Big Game Committee, Official Measurers, Correspondence, 1957-1989 (Box-folder 159/7-8)
    - Requests, 1998 (Box-folder 160/1-3)
    - Requests for Official Measurer Certification, Canada and Foreign, 1973-1982 (Box-folder 160/4-5)
    - Seminars on Measuring and Scoring, 1967 (Box-folder 160/6)
    - Training and Review Outlines, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 160/7)
    - Training Workshop, 1976 and undated (Box-folder 160/8)
    - Training Workshop, 1983-1994 (Box-folder 160/9)
    - Vitae of Official Measurers, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 160/10)
  - National Collection of Heads and Horns, 1906-2002; Subseries 5; 2.75 linear feet
    The National Collection of Heads and Horns was established by Club member William T. Hornaday and was displayed at the Bronx Zoo in New York City beginning in 1922. The collection is currently held at the Buffalo Bill Historical Center in Cody, Wyoming and is maintained by the Boone and Crockett Club.
    This subseries contains correspondence, committee reports, inventories dating from 1906 through 1978, promotional materials, and trophy prints. Of particular interest are the research notes of Lowell E. Baier which provide a history of the National Collection of Heads and Horns.
    - A Listing of the More Desirable Trophies, by Donald T. Carter, 1956-1977 (Box-folder 161/1)
    - Appraisal, 1973-1983 (Box-folder 161/2)
    - Lowell E. Baier and William H. Nesbitt, Correspondence, 1978 (Box-folder 161/3)
    - Lowell E. Baier, Research Notes, 1981 and undated (Box-folder 161/4-5)
    - Commitment to the Buffalo Bill Historical Center, 1990 (Box-folder 161/6)
    - Agreement with Buffalo Bill Historical Center and The Boone and Crockett Club, 1998-2002 (Box-folder 228/9)
    - Buffalo Bill Historical Center, Bronson Sculpture Project, 1983 (Box-folder 161/7)
    - Buffalo Bill Historical Center, Chadwick Ram Bronze Agreement, 1990 (Box-folder 161/8)
    - Buffalo Bill Historical Center, Firearms Donations, 1992 (Box-folder 161/9)
    - Buffalo Bill Historical Center, Sand Bar Rendezvous, Correspondence and Event Materials, 1989 (Box-folder 161/10)
    - Buffalo Bill Historical Center, Bob Scriver, Theodore Roosevelt Bronze, 1991 (Box-folder 161/11)
    - Captions for Displays, undated (Box-folder 161/12)
    - Certificate Materials, 1991 (Box-folder 161/13)
    - Certificate Typeset Proofs, undated (Box-folder 161/14)
    - Chadwick Ram Brochure, Galley Proofs and Draft, 1980 (Box-folder 161/15)
    - Chadwick Ram Bronze, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 161/16)
    - Chadwick Ram Print, Donor List, 1980 (Box-folder 161/17)
    - Cody Firearms Museum, Grand Opening Souvenir Edition Newsletter, 1991 (Box-folder 161/18)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1960-1977 (Box-folder 161/19 (1 of 3))
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1960-1977 (Box-folder 162/1-2 (2-3 of 3))
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 162/3-6)
    - Dispersals of Specimens, Correspondence, 1960-1977 (Box-folder 162/7)
    - Donations, 1990 (Box-folder 162/8)
    - Exhibit Inventory, 1963 (Box-folder 162/9)
    - Foundation for North American Wild Sheep, Chadwick Ram Casting, 1991 (Box-folder 162/10)
    - Fred Bear Foundation, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 162/11)
    - Inventory Part I, 1907 (Box-folder 162/12)
    - Inventory Part II, 1908 (Box-folder 162/13)
    - Inventory, circa 1942 (Box-folder 163/1)
    - Inventory and Prints, circa 1974 (Box-folder OS 219/x)
    - Inventory, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 163/2)
    - Inventory, 1978 (Box-folder OS 219/x)
    - Invitation to View Exhibition at Buffalo Bill Historical Center, undated (Box-folder 163/3)
    - Limited Edition Booklet, Originals, undated (Box-folder 163/4)
    - List of Specimens and Guide Book to the Collection, 1931 (Box-folder 163/5)
    - Listing of the More Desirable Game Trophies, 1956 (Box-folder 163/6)
    - Miscellaneous Notes, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 163/7-8)
    - New York Zoological Society Special Report, 1936 (Box-folder 163/9)
    - Photographs, undated (Box-folder 163/10)
    - Preliminary Official Catalogue of the National Collection of Head and Horns, 1906 (Box-folder 164/1)
    - Press Releases, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 164/2)
    - Proposal for Disposition of Collection, 1977 (Box-folder 164/3)
    - Record Holder Catalog, 1971 (Box-folder 164/4)
    - Records Ledger, 1919-1960 (Box-folder 164/5)
    - Second Edition Catalog, Correspondence, 1992 (Box-folder 164/6)
    - Sheep Brochure, 1980 (Box-folder 164/7)
    - Special Report of Committee, 1936 (Box-folder 164/8)
    - Status Reports, 1933-1977 (Box-folder 164/9)
    - Status Reports with Recommended Actions, 1955-1978 (Box-folder 164/10)
    - Stolen Moose Antlers Police Report, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 165/1)
    - Transfer of Collection to Boone and Crockett Club, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 165/2)
    - Trophy Prints, circa 1974 (Box-folder OS 219/x)
- Communications, 1904-2009; Series IV; 18.0 linear feet
  This series documents the Boone and Crockett Club’s outreach, publicity, promotions and publications. The series has been divided into four subseries and includes correspondence, drafts of publications, materials related to the Club’s Fair Chase magazine, the Club’s newsletter, the Club’s Associate’s Program and licensing and copyright materials.
  Materials in this series arrived at the archives with no discernable original order to the files and were grouped and interfiled by the processor to reflect historic and current organization of the Club’s communications division. Series are arranged alphabetically.
  - Publications, 1910-2009; Subseries 1; 15.375 linear feet
    An Editorial Committee was formed at the first official meeting of the Boone and Crockett Club in 1888, and the Club has published materials related to big game, conservation, and hunting since 1893. This subseries contains five sub-subseries which include materials related to the Club’s published materials.
    - Administration, 1910-2000; Sub-subseries 1; 3.75 linear feet
      This sub-subseries contains materials created by both the Editorial and Historical committees of the Boone and Crockett Club from the late 1950s through the late 1980s, as well as materials created by paid professional staff. Items include committee meeting minutes, correspondence, book orders, inventories, and publication lists. Absent are materials related to items published before 1910.
      - Abercrombie and Fitch, Correspondence, 1991 (Box-folder 165/3)
      - Book Flyers, 1991 (Box-folder 165/4)
      - Book Inventories, 1911-1912 (Box-folder 165/5)
      - Book Inventory, Alexandria Office, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 165/6)
      - Book Order Information, 1973-1981 (Box-folder 165/7)
      - Book Order Ledger, 1976-1981 (Box-folder 165/8)
      - Book Orders, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 165/9)
      - Book Orders, 1976 (Box-folder 165/10)
      - Book Orders, Completed, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 165/11)
      - Book Orders, Originals, 1987 and undated (Box-folder 165/12)
      - Book Plate, circa 1960 (Box-folder 165/13)
      - Book Plate, Correspondence, 1956-1959 (Box-folder 165/14)
      - Book Printing Negotiations, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 165/15)
      - Book Returns and Charge Problems, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 165/16)
      - Book Reviews, 1976-1991 (Box-folder 165/17)
      - Canadian Hunting Publications Incorporated, 1992 (Box-folder 165/18)
      - Club Book/Item Dealer List, 1991 (Box-folder 165/19-20)
      - Communications Committee, The American Outdoorsman, 1991 (Box-folder 166/1)
      - Complimentary Copy Cover Letter, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 166/2)
      - Complimentary Copy Recipient Ledger, 1981-1987 (Box-folder 166/3)
      - Complimentary Copy Recipient Ledger, 1981-1987 (Box-folder 166/4)
      - Complimentary Copy Recipient Ledger, 1986-1993 (Box-folder 166/5)
      - Complimentary Copy Recipient Ledger, 1988-1994 (Box-folder 166/6)
      - Correspondence, 1910-1938 (Box-folder 166/7)
      - Charles Sheldon, Correspondence, 1920-1926 (Box-folder 166/8)
      - Correspondence and Invoices, 1939-1951 (Box-folder 166/9-10)
      - Correspondence, Memoranda, and Reports, 1952-1961 (Box-folder 166/11)
      - Correspondence, Invoices, and Receipts, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 167/1)
      - Correspondence, 1977-1982 (Box-folder 167/2)
      - Customer Complaints, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 167/3)
      - Directory Listings, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 167/4)
      - Distribution of Records Book Flyers, 1978 (Box-folder 167/5)
      - Editorial and Historical Committee, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 167/6)
      - Editorial and Historical Committee, Correspondence, Memoranda, and Reports, 1959 (Box-folder 167/7)
      - Editorial and Historical Committee, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1960 (Box-folder 167/8-9)
      - Editorial and Historical Committee, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1961 (Box-folder 167/10-11)
      - Editorial and Historical Committee, Correspondence, 1962-1969 (Box-folder 168/1)
      - Editorial and Historical Committee, Stackpole Books Publishing, 1962-1973 (Box-folder 169/2)
      - Editorial Committee, Meeting Minutes, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 168/3)
      - Editorial Committee, Correspondence, Memoranda, and Reports, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 168/4-6)
      - Editorial and Historical Committee, James C. Rikhoff, Correspondence, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 168/7)
      - Editorial and Historical Committee, Reports, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 168/8)
      - Editorial and Historical Committee, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 169/1-2)
      - Editorial Committee, Publication Complaints from Recipients, 1975 (Box-folder 169/3)
      - Editorial and Historical Committee, Correspondence, Memoranda, and Reports, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 169/4)
      - Editorial and Historical Committee, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 169/5)
      - Exchanged and Replaced Publications, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 169/6)
      - Falcon Press, Correspondence, Invoices, and Receipts, 1988-1993 (Box-folder 169/7)
      - Field and Stream Book Club, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 169/8)
      - Historical and Publicity Committee, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1948-1970 (Box-folder 169/9)
      - Hunting and Outdoor Films, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 169/10)
      - In the Blood, Hunting Film, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 169/11)
      - Library of Congress Cataloging Information, undated (Box-folder 169/12)
      - Limited Edition Books, Sale Ledger, 1981-1990 (Box-folder 170/1)
      - Lost Book Orders, Correspondence, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 170/2)
      - J.J. McBride, Inventories and Notes, 1992 (Box-folder 170/3)
      - Meredith Book Club, 1972-1992 (Box-folder 170/4)
      - New Edition and Book Proposals, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 170/5)
      - Nutri-Books Corporation, 1985 (Box-folder 170/6)
      - Order Inquiries, 1976-1980 (Box-folder 170/7)
      - Out of Print Publications, 1959-1970 (Box-folder 170/8)
      - Outdoor Editor Form Letter, 1991 (Box-folder 170/9)
      - Outdoor Life Book Club, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 170/10)
      - Outdoor Life, Article, Responses, 1984 (Box-folder 170/11)
      - Outdoor Writers, Correspondence, 1984-1989 (Box-folder 170/12)
      - Outdoor Writers, List, undated (Box-folder 170/13)
      - Pacific Pipeline, Incorporated, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 170/14)
      - Pro Forma Notes, undated (Box-folder 170/15)
      - Problem Orders, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 170/16)
      - Publication Agreement, 1913 (Box-folder 170/17)
      - Publication Charges, 1914 (Box-folder 170/18)
      - Publication Inventory, 1992 (Box-folder 170/19)
      - Publication List, undated (Box-folder 170/20)
      - Publication Purchasing Ledger, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 170/21 (1 of 2))
      - Publication Purchasing Ledger, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 171/1 (2 of 2))